<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
    <title>Internal Postings</title>
    <link>http://localhost:8080/hr/feeds/rss.xml</link>
    <description>Daffron iXp Products</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 10:06:33 CST</pubDate>
	     <item>
	         <title>Consumer Information System</title>
	         <link>http://www.daffron.com/solution/cis.aspx</link>
	         <description>A fully configurable system to meet your needs today and tomorrow.  System features 
	           include: Consumer Accounting System; Multi-service - electric, water, gas; Non-metered billing 
	           including outside of service territory ...</description>
	     </item>
	     <item>
             <title>eBusiness</title>
             <link>http://www.daffron.com/solution/ebusiness.aspx</link>
             <description>Daffron offers a fully automated billing and payment service, providing an end-to-end 
                solution from the customer all the way to depositing funds into a utility’s bank account. Through 
                collaboration with ...</description>
         </item>
         <item>
             <title>Financial Management System</title>
             <link>http://www.daffron.com/solution/fms.aspx</link>
             <description>The Daffron Financial Management applications integrate with all other software 
                solutions across the utility’s business. The goal is to automate your enterprise and streamline 
                your business processes ...</description>
         </item>
         <item>
             <title>Materials Management System</title>
             <link>http://www.daffron.com/solution/mms.aspx</link>
             <description>Daffron Materials Management Software is easy to use yet comprehensive business 
                management software that provides users with the tools needed to make educated decisions.  
                The software manages all aspects ...</description>
         </item>
         <item>
             <title>Staking</title>
             <link>http://www.daffron.com/solution/staking.aspx</link>
             <description>Daffron developed StakingiXp to drive work order automation, creating front-end 
                digital data sources for CIS, GIS, and other back-end systems. Stakers, using tablet PC’s 
                or laptops, perform design work ...</description>
         </item>
         <item>
             <title>Geograpical Information System</title>
             <link>http://www.daffron.com/solution/gis.aspx</link>
             <description>Electric and gas utilities have long recognized the importance of accurate 
                facility maps and records. Maps have been used in utilities for many years. Workers 
                need them to find ...</description>
         </item>
         <item>
             <title>Incident (Outage) Management</title>
             <link>http://www.daffron.com/solution/ims.aspx</link>
             <description>When it comes to interruption in service, most utilities agree that the 
                two most important priorities are finding and fixing the problem as quickly as possible 
                to restore service and the flow ...</description>
         </item>
         <item>
             <title>Mobile Field Force</title>
             <link>http://www.daffron.com/solution/mobilefieldforce.aspx</link>
             <description>As part of our iXp enterprise solution strategy for utilities, Daffron 
                & Associates, Inc. has added an exciting Vehicle Location and Mobile Field Force 
                Solutions partner ...</description>
         </item>
         <item>
             <title>Toolbox</title>
             <link>http://www.daffron.com/solution/toolbox.aspx</link>
             <description>Today, utility organizations must meet the dual objectives of 
                network reliability and proactive customer service. This challenge is impossible 
                to meet without successfully integrating ...</description>
         </item>
    </channel>
</rss>